http://www.middleatlantic.com/privacy-policy.aspx

Shipping Impact:
Upcoming holiday hours. Click for the latest.
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to Legrand North America, Inc. (LNA). This statement discloses the information practices for LNA Web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared. LNA Web sites include any and all Web sites of LNA's related companies, including but not limited to Cablofil Inc., Ortronics, Inc., Legrand Home Systems, Inc. (formerly OnQ Inc. and Vantage Controls, Inc.), Legrand Canada, Inc., The Watt Stopper, Inc., The Wiremold Company, and BTicino US.
Personal information
In general, you can visit LNA on the Internet without telling us who you are and without giving any personal information about yourself. There are times, however, when we or our partners may need information from you. You may choose to give us personal information in a variety of situations. For example, you may want to give us information, such as your name and address or e-mail address, to correspond with you, to process an order. You may give us your credit card details to buy something from us or a description of your education and work experience in connection with a job opening at LNA for which you wish to be considered. We intend to let you know how we will use such information before we collect it from you; if you tell us that you do not want us to use this information to make further contact with you beyond fulfilling your requests, we will respect your wishes. If you give us personal information about somebody else, such as a spouse or work colleague, we will assume that you have their permission to do so.
Using and Sharing Personal Information
The following paragraphs describe in more detail how LNA may use your personal information and with whom we may share it. Depending on the type of LNA Web site you are visiting, one or more of the paragraphs may apply. For example, if you order a product from an LNA Web site, your information will be handled as described in such paragraphs as Fulfilling Your Transaction Request and Marketing Use.
Fulfilling your transaction request
If you request something from an LNA Web site, for example, a product or service, a callback, or specific marketing materials, we will use the information you provide to fulfill your request. To help us do this, we may share information, with others, for instance, other parts of LNA, LNA's resellers or distributors, financial institutions, shipping companies, postal or government authorities (for example, Customs authorities) involved in fulfilling your request. In connection with a transaction we may also contact you as part of our customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.
If you choose to "Email This Page" to a friend or colleague, we will ask for their name and email address. We will automatically send a one-time email sharing the page you indicated. LNA does not store this information.
Marketing Use
The information you provide to LNA on certain LNA Web sites may also be used by LNA and selected third parties for marketing purposes. Before we use it, however, we will offer you the opportunity to choose whether or not to have your information used in this way. To opt-out of receiving further marketing emails from LNA, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each email.
LNA Human Resources Web Sites, such as "Careers" on the LNA home page
In connection with a job application or inquiry, whether advertised on an LNA Web site or otherwise, you may provide us with information about yourself, such as a resume or curriculum vitae. We may use this information throughout LNA and its related entities for the purpose of employment consideration or your inquiry. Except where you tell us not to, we will keep the information for future consideration.
Information for resellers and/or distributors
If you represent an LNA resellers and/or distributor, you may visit an LNA Web site intended specifically for LNA resellers and/or distributors, or subscribe to an account on a non-public Web sites such as the Service Center. We may use information provided on any such site to administer and develop our business relationship with you, the resellers or distributors you represent, and LNA resellers and/or distributors generally. For instance, this may involve using your information to send you details of LNA resellers and/or distributor programs. It may also include sharing certain information with other resellers and/or distributors (subject to any confidentiality obligations that may exist), or LNA customers or prospects, for example, if you participate in our programs via SalesForce.com. In connection with a particular transaction or program, we may also contact you as part of customer satisfaction surveys or for market research purposes.
LNA Supplier Administration
If you represent an LNA supplier, you may visit an LNA Web site intended specifically for use by LNA suppliers, or subscribe to an account on a non-public Web sites such as the Service Center. We may use the information provided on any such site in connection with entering into or performing a transaction with you. For example, this may include sharing information with other parts of LNA, LNA's resellers and/or distributors, customers, shipping companies, financial institutions, postal or government authorities involved in fulfillment. It may also be used to administer and develop our relationship with you, the supplier you represent and/or other LNA suppliers generally.
Use of Information in the Social Networking Environment
LNA may facilitate the use of social computing tools on some of its Web sites to enable online sharing and collaboration among members who have registered to use them. These include forums, wikis, blogs and other social media platforms.
When registering to use these tools, you will be asked to provide certain personal information to LNA. Depending on the platform, you may be agreeing to allow certain of the information you provide to be displayed as part of a public profile in the social networking environment in which you are registering to participate. Registration information which is not automatically made available to other participants as part any public profile will be subject to and protected in accordance with this privacy statement.
Any other content you post, such as pictures, information, opinions, or any other type of personal information which you make available to other participants on these social platforms, is not subject to this privacy statement. Rather, such content is subject to the Terms of Use applicable to whichever forum, wiki, blog or other social media platform on which you are posting. Furthermore, additional guidelines and privacy policy information may be identified for your attention in regard of your use of such social media.. Please make sure you review the Terms of Use and other policies applicable to any social media in which you elect to participate to better understand your, LNA's, and other parties' rights and obligations with regard to such content. In addition, you should be aware that the content you post on any such social computing platforms may be made broadly available to others inside and outside LNA.
Other LNA Web Site Notices
In some cases, specific LNA Web sites may contain other notices about their use and the information practices applicable to those sites.
Information Security and Quality
We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its quality. We implement appropriate measures and processes, such as using encryption when transmitting certain sensitive information, to help us to keep your information secure and to maintain its quality during transmission.
Supplementing Information
From time to time we may supplement information you give us via an LNA Web site with information from other sources, such as information validating your address or other available information about businesses. This is to help us maintain the accuracy of the information we collect and to help us provide a better service.
Use of Suppliers
In some cases LNA uses suppliers to collect, use, analyze and otherwise process information on its behalf. It is LNA's practice to require such suppliers to handle information in a manner consistent with LNA's policies.
Mergers and Acquisitions
Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, LNA decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from sellers. It is LNA's practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.
Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Technologies
We sometimes collect non-identifiable information from visits to our Web sites to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit, and we also measure visitor activity on LNA Web sites, but we do so in ways that keep the information non-identifiable. LNA or others on LNA's behalf may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service.
Also, when we collect personal data from you in a transaction, we may extract some information about that transaction in a non-identifiable format and combine it with other non-identifiable information such as clickstream data. This information is used and analyzed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patterns. This information is not stored or reviewed at an individual level. If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner you can disable your cookies.
We collect the information we mentioned in the previous paragraphs through the use of various technologies, including one called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer but not you. Some LNA pages use cookies, sent by LNA or its third party vendors, or other technologies to better serve you when you return to the Web site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some Web sites may not work properly.
Some LNA Web sites also use Web beacon or other technologies to better tailor those sites to provide better customer service. These technologies may be in use on a number of pages across LNA's Web sites. When a visitor accesses these pages, a non-identifiable notice of that visit is generated which may be processed by us or by our suppliers. These Web beacons usually work in conjunction with cookies. If you don't want your cookie information to be associated with your visits to these pages, you can set your browser to turn off cookies.
Service Quality Monitoring
Certain Web transactions may also involve you calling us or our calling you. Please be aware that it is LNA's general practice to monitor and in some cases record such calls for staff training or quality assurance purposes.
Disclosures Required By Law
Please be aware that in certain circumstances, it is possible that personal information may be subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, or orders.
Links to non-LNA Web sites
LNA Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. LNA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other Web sites.
Notification of Changes
This privacy statement was last updated on [ ], 2009. A notice will be posted on our Web site home page for 30 days whenever this privacy statement is changed in a material way.
Privacy Questions and Access
If you have a question about this statement or LNA's handling of your information, you can send an email to the LNA Web site coordinator. The address for this is webmaster@legrand.us. You can also contact us at:
Legrand North America 60 Woodlawn StreetWest Hartford, CT 06110Attention: Webmaster
If you wish to obtain a copy of particular information you provided to LNA, or if you become aware the information is incorrect and you would like us to correct it contact us at webmaster@legrand.us.
Before LNA is able to provide you with any information or correct any inaccuracies, however, we may ask you to verify your identity and to provide other details to help us to respond to your request. We will contact you within 30 days your request.
This Web site is maintained by the Legrand North America, Inc.
1008580-CD3
